Mon!
Oh, my God!
Sorry.
- Hi, Arci, welcome. - Hello.
[Filipina Actress Arci Muñoz]
- Hello.
- Sorry, sorry.
Jodi!
We're so loud when we speak Filipino.
- Long time! Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- Hello!
- Take a seat!
Stay here for now.
- Arci, we're still practicing.
- It's okay.
Please sit here for now.
- Stay here for now, sorry.
- Okay.
Yes.
Kumusta!
"Kumusta" is...
"How have you been?"
In Korean.
[Kumusta]
[The Big Table]
- Jodi.
- How are you?
When did you guys get here?
The other, other, other day.
We've been here a week.
Well, I've been here a week.
- You've been here for a week?
- One week.
But I'll be staying.
I will stay for one more week.
But I always come back and forth.
- Korea is like a second home.
- Oh, my gosh.
There's so much to see.
So I come here almost every month.
I'm so jealous.
You're so fluent in Korean.
I'm not fluent. Oh my gosh, no.
I'm like, how do we even
run a restaurant with...
I mean, so how do you do it?
Well, we're just, I guess,
blessed to have customers
who kind of understand
broken Korean, or if not...
Charades!
You just have to describe.
Oh, earlier, I couldn't explain the pork.
So I just said: "Oink oink."
Oh, my gosh!
- Oh, my God!
What do you want to drink?
I ordered beer.
Beer! Oh, right.
Sorry, we got distracted by the chit-chat.
Beer
for you.
Oh, thank you. Appreciate it.
- Thank you, Jodi!
- Okay.
Order 9 is for Arci.
- That one?
- Yes.
Sinigang, inasal, palabok, halo-halo.
Get ready on the order of Arci.
Let's just serve them everything,
so that her diet fails.
I'm starving.
Oh, my gosh.
You didn't give Chef
the order for table number...
- One?
- What?
- Yeah. It's still here.
- Did I not give it?
Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry!
Chef, sorry, my bad.
I didn't give you the order for Table 1.
Table 1 is...
I'm so sorry.
That was when Arci arrived.
Okay.
I'm so sorry!
- No worries.
- We'll just kind of...
entertain them, I'll give them whatever.
Yeah, we'll give them a free something.
We'll jump. Let's prioritize this.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, it's okay.
Okay.
I am sorry for the delay.
Because of that, I'll give you...
A special treat.
- Sorry.
- Oh, thank you.
For... For waiting. Sorry.
Thank you.
This is for you.
Oh, this looks better, right?
So, in total, we have two sini...
- Okay, let's do one at a time.
- Yeah, two Sinigang.
- Yeah.
Okay.
This doesn't have enough water.
Sinigang for Table 1.
And then...
That's it.
Palabok...
Table 1.
Hello, sorry for the wait.
This is your sinigang.
Let me get your bowls for you.
This smells familiar.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Here.
Smells like ginseng chicken soup.
Yes, it's actually like a pork back-bone stew,
but this one is more...
- Ah, pork back-bone stew?
- Sour?
It's more... it's more sour.
Filipino style!
- Sour?
- Yes.
It's Filipino style.
Wow.
- Oh, thank you!
- Here.
Enjoy!
- Thank you!
I've never had food
with this type of sour taste before.
This is good!
- Oh, it's sour.
- Yeah.
My style, my style.
Here's your palabok.
Please enjoy!
- Wow!
- Thank you!
Wow!
This looks so good.
This kind of reminds me of curry.
- It's kinda like glass noodles.
- The portions are huge.
How is it?
That is so good.
No, seriously, that's so good.
I'm giving them...
I'm giving Table 1 an extra portion.
Because we...
- Of inasal?
- Yeah.
I'll just say it's a little gift for them.
Yes. And then say, "We apologize for..."
The waiting.
Okay.
Hi, this is your garlic rice.
And you ordered one chicken inasal,
but we made it two.
Just as a "sorry" for the waiting.
- Okay, thank you.
- Yes.
Please enjoy!
Wow!
I wanted to try these together.
Good? Good?
No good!
Very good!
I'm just so happy
because nobody is making complaints.
If ever we do receive complaints,
Then we'll just have to say: "Sorry, sorry..."
There's nothing we can do. Just say sorry.
If someone says, "We don't like it",
I'll be like, "Alright, I'll have it then."
You'll be paying for them anyway.
This is...
Her sinigang.
Then we'll serve the palabok and inasal?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay.
Sinigang, please for Ms. Arci.
Okay!
Alright.
Okay.
Good evening!
Hi!
We're serving you your palabok.
- Oh, my God.
- And your plain rice.
- Hi, good evening.
- Hi!
- Hi, Chef.
- Hello, how are you?
I think we've met each other
in an event in Dubai.
During "Global Filipino".
Oh, my gosh, it's a long time ago.
With Martin?
Yeah, I think so.
Please sit down, enjoy your meal.
- Inasal, palabok, and then...
- Thank you, Chef.
- Okay, sure.
- Go ahead.
Let's eat!
- You guys eat first.
- Enjoy.
Is it delicious?
Oh, this is good.
Delicious.
You know what the best sinigang
I've ever tasted is?
In New York.
- Wow.
- "Wow", really?
Wow, it was so delicious.
Let's change that, Arci.
Let's make that
the best sinigang you've ever had.
Correct. Yes.
It's in Korea!
Yes!
What are the odds?
Your best sinigang is not in the Philippines,
but in New York, and now, here in Korea.
She cooked it and...
She made it.
You're the one who cooked?
- Some of it. The sinigang, yes.
- The sinigang.
Wow!
What did you say?
You tried the one from New York?
No, she said, like, she tasted
the best sinigang in New York.
And now, it's going to be Korea.
What?
Which...
There's this restaurant in New York
that I always go to. Oh, my God.
- Tradisyon?
- Tradisyon!
- That's my friend.
- Oh, my gosh, their sinigang.
Yeah, but now here, it's in Korea.
- Go tell him...
- What?
Say: "Anton! Someone beat your sinigang."
Yes.
Next time, they won't serve you
any sinigang in New York.
Thank you, Chef, for the food.
- Say hi to Anton.
- I will!
Oh, my gosh, see? Small world.
Hello!
Good evening.
So, would you like to check your bill?
- Thank you, take care.
- Goodbye.
Sleep well. Good night.
Bye-bye.
- Thank you, Jodi.
- Thank you, sir.
Bye-bye.
How are you doing, sweetie?
- This is...
- Are you tired?
The life of an OFW.
Life's really like this here in Korea.
It's tough, but we manage.
You can do it! Fighting!
Fighting!
Wow, just wow.
There's a lot to clean up.
I'm getting overwhelmed over here.
We'll be able to clean this.
We're many.
Hello!
Can we get the bill?
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry, auntie.
Just call me sis.
"Auntie" might be a little too much.
Okay.
Jodi!
Cashier.
- Aw, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for coming.
- Good food, good service.
- Thank you.
- Jodi.
Thank you.
Take care.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Bye-bye.
I stink.
Thank you!
- Bye-bye. Good night.
- Thank you.
Take care.
We can flip the sign now, right?
I think so.
[Closed]
Wow.
Okay.
Let's start.
Excuse me.
Yuck.
Now I know why they tell you
to finish your food.
- Sorry, Lord.
- That's a lot of waste, huh?
- A lot.
- Oh, sorry.
- That's a lot.
- Sorry, Lord.
Let's do this first.
I'll just put them here.
Okay, go.
There's still so much left.
Heavy!
Voilá.
Those are being cleaned now.
Maybe you can put them in the right...
I miss my dog.
I miss...
I miss everybody.
Sorry, Chef. I'll handle it.
I'll just do this first.
Almost done, almost done.
I want to check the time.
I need air, I need air!
Wait, my legs...
I wonder what's going to happen to us tomorrow.
I don't think I could be a dishwasher.
- You think you can't?
- I don't think I can.
The whole day?
Respect to the dishwasher.
- Yes!
- Geez.
And then when you call the waiter,
you'll call them with so much respect now,
because you know how hard it is.
Insane.
[All Clear]
Yeah!
Ah!
Good Lord.
My foot is hurting.
Is it bad to have that feeling when you...
When you have one last customer,
you're thinking:
"Can you just leave already..."
It's normal.
I will never be the last customer
- in any restaurant.
- Don't. Don't.
Never eat on the last call.
I'm so sorry to all the restaurants
I've been a pain at.
I don't even have energy to celebrate.
Me, too.
But her... Wow. She got burned, but...
I thought...
She was unfazed.
Gotta do what you gotta do.
As for her, I saw the...
She's smiling, but you can see
- she's not really happy.
- Me?
- Her.
- No, me.
Ah, I thought...
It's slowly coming out...
- Exhaustion.
- Your eyes!
It's really obvious when you're tired.
- Yeah.
- Super.
I remember even when we...
On the set of "Be Careful with My Heart."
When we were working.
- The eyes. They don't lie.
- Never lie.
Ah, what a day.
I can't wait for my cheeseburger.
Tomorrow's another day and I think...
We need help!
- Yeah, because remember...
- Were we like that before?
It's so hard to wash the dishes and like,
cook at the same time.
And you guys are serving.
Maybe we should hire someone.
We can't do it, just the four of us.
Two people running the front of the house,
two people running the kitchen?
Oh, Lord.
Oh my God!
Okay, what if, I mean I don't know.
Would you give in and ask for help?
Maybe we need one more.
But the thing is, who could it be?
- Okay.
Alright, let's clean up and go home.
Yeah.
Ouch.
[Close 10:30 PM]
[Yeongdong Traditional Market]
This is the market.
I'm excited for this.
Oh, my God. Wow, their market!
It's extremely clean and calm.
- Look at their rice cakes!
- I know!
So...
What we have to buy is sea bream?
- Yes.
- Sea bream.
Pork knuckles.
Wow!
Pork knuckles are a thing here?
Is that famous here?
I don't know, but it's nice.
It smells sweet.
But we're here for fish.
Okay. Eyes on the prize.
- Okay.
Are we not allowed to buy food?
Let's buy later,
but we have to get the fish first.
Okay.
We have a new dish today, right?
- And it's a sea bream.
- Yeah.
- Salt-crusted.
- Yes.
And they're going to love it.
Okay.
But right now, we're like...
I mean, we're like a kid in the candy store.
I'm getting distracted.
- Look at this.
- Oh, kimchi.
Wait.
Okay, I also want to take a picture of this.
Oh, wow. There are different kinds of kimchi.
I know!
Look at their rice cakes!
Wait, that looks so good.
Oh, that's so cute.
Wait a second.
This got my attention.
Cute.
Oh, it says Philippines. Look.
What?
The thingy!
Pilipinas!
- There it is!
- There.
I thought I smelled something fishy,
and here it is.
Look at this.
It's so fresh.
Hi.
Hello.
- Hi! Hello!
- Hello.
How are you?
What are we looking for?
Sea bream.
- Domi?
Ah, this one.
There, it's not slimy.
Then...
There!
What's that?
You can see how fresh it is.
- Ah, okay.
- Then you smell it.
You can smell that?
I can't.
Gimme your...
It's not... It smells like the sea.
Ah, okay.
And the eyes, they're crystal clear.
That means they're still fresh?
Yes, it's not cloudy.
Okay.
Should we get...
Can you ask him how much?
- How much is it?
- 15,000 won.
1,500...
Ah, okay, and then the discount.
Discount, please?
No, this is already cheap.
We charge only the cost price.
- Okay.
- He doesn't want to.
Okay, okay. No problem.
How many?
Let's get a few. Let's get maybe...
Fifteen pieces?
- Fifteen pieces?
- Yeah.
So, that's around one box?
I think so.
Can I get one box, please?
Okay, here you go.
- Mission accomplished.
- Yes.
Picture!
He's so cute.
Okay, thank you!
Another day?
I think we're the last ones to get here.
The late ones.
I hope everything is okay.
Alright.
Hi! Good morning!
- Good morning!
- Hey guys!
Right on cue!
- Hello!
- She's here!
Good morning!
I'm Ramona, nice to meet you.
Welcome to Korea!
We need help.
Maybe we should hire someone.
Okay, she told me earlier:
"I'll be here for a week."
You think she would?
Hello?
Jodi, is that you?
- Yes, it's me.
- Is this you?
Yes, it's me!
Yes, Jodi!
Did you like the food earlier?
Yes. It was good. Delicious.
Are you going to be busy tomorrow?
Tomorrow...
I was just planning to wander around,
but nothing much.
I'm not busy.
If your plans
aren't super important tomorrow...
Then maybe you can chill out
here in our resto...
If it's okay, if it's okay!
I guess it's okay.
I can drop everything tomorrow.
We love you.
Jodi, you've got to remember that I'm here.
I'm like...
I am Korean. Just kidding.
What was that?
I'm basically Korean, I'm Korean.
We'll serve the fish
and the chicken together with the rice.
One sinigang, one gising-gising,
one halo-halo, please!
It's really slippery.
- One more fish.
- Yeah.
One more palabok.
And gising-gising.
- Thank you!
Come this way, is that okay?
Garlic rice.
Enjoy your meal.
[Arci Muñoz All Rounder]
Nice!
- Give me a hug!
- What's up, ketchup?
What's up, ketchup?
[17 minutes to go]
Seventeen minutes.
Okay. Ready?
Okay, I'm good with the appetizer.
Alright. Garlic, onions...
and lemongrass.
Just three things.
This partner of mine...
She's only been in the kitchen for two days.
But it's like...
Like she's been here for a week.
Imagine after one week,
it's going to feel like a month in.
Sorry, I'm just pressuring you.
I'm just trying to toughen you up.
You might jinx it.
Kitchens do have some pressure.
For me, when I cook,
I don't want anyone in the kitchen.
I want just me.
Yeah.
I don't like people watching me
when I'm cooking.
Okay, we open!
I'll open it up now.
- Yes, sweetheart.
- Okay.
[Day 2]
[12:00 PM]
[Today's Menu: Sea Bream]
This is salt-crusted sea bream.
Our signature dish for today.
We're open!
- Restaurant's open!
- Okay.
This is it. My dreams are really coming true.
To become a chef. Joke.
Hi!
Hi.
- Hello!
- Hello, countrymen!
- Hello.
Filipino!
Oh, Philippines!
- Hello! How are you?
- Philippines!
- Thank you for coming!
- Yes, hello.
I've heard there's something interesting here.
And that's why I came.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes.
- And I want to give it a try.
- Have a seat for a moment.
- Sit down for a bit.
Is it okay if I take some videos?
- No problem.
- For my vlog!
Go ahead.
Are you okay to sit here?
Anyway, thank you for coming.
- Of course!
- It's so...
- Okay, so this is our menu.
- Oh, alright.
- There you go.
- Okay.
Well, it's nice to see
Filipino cuisine here in Korea.
True.
Of course, I would want to try the sinigang.
Okay.
And I would also like to have gising-gising.
So that we "wake up".
And of course, the halo-halo.
Okay, halo-halo.
- Even if it's cold.
- Its cold.
So, for now, we'll prepare your order.
- Alright! Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
And then, we'll give you a special treat.
Okay, alright. What is it?
- Secret! Once we return.
- Secret?
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
There you go.
- Okay!
- An order!
Oh, dear. What is it?
One sinigang, one gising-gising,
one halo-halo, please!
There's gising-gising as well?
- Yes.
- Oh, okay.
So, I'll do the sinigang.
But the broth isn't ready yet.
- Make it fast.
- Alright, alright.
You're out for now.
There we go.
So we'll do some vlogging here first.
This restaurant is so pretty.
Kumusta. It's very Filipino.
There. Hello!
Okay, so as our special treat for you...
Wow, the special treat is here!
So, what the chef prepared
is banchan, or side dishes.
And then, our welcome drink,
calamansi.
Calamansi juice.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
Dilis.
For the dilis, you can taste the mango.
You can really taste it. Yum!
For me,
it's the chicken skin.
It's just perfect.
Sinigang veggies.
- What's next after that?
- Okay.
Okay.
Sinigang is ready.
Thank you!
Okay, gising-gising is ready.
- So, this is your gising-gising.
- Hello.
- Wow! Gising-gising is here.
- Here it is.
We have sinigang
and gising-gising.
Okay!
Food is ready!
I wonder what this tastes like.
Let's go!
Oh, Lord.
Lord, what did I do to deserve this sinigang?
Yum!
By far the best sinigang that I've tried
aside from my mom's sinigang.
Yum!
Hello!
- How many?
- Five.
Five.
Five!
This way, please.
Please follow me.
Welcome to Kumusta!
- Here's your menu.
- Welcome.
It's like they suddenly flooded in...
Yeah.
Hello!
- Ready to order?
- Yes.
Okay.
We want this one,
this one, this one.
Thank you very much.
Yes?
- I think I'll go for the inasal with the rice.
- Okay.
Okay.
One gising-gising,
one palabok, two inasal, two garlic rice.
One fish.
- There's fish?
- Yes!
Oh my God, our orders are piling up.
Hi!
There are quite a lot of options.
I'll have...
[1 Palabok]
Palabok, please.
[2 Palabok]
I will have Palabok as well.
[3 Palabok]
Hi.
[4 Palabok]
We all ordered Palabok.
[5 Palabok]
Same here, Palabok, please.
[Palabok for Everyone]
- Palabok. - Everyone...
- Okay, so...
- All Palabok.
One, two, three, four, five. Five palabok.
It's one like, this big plate, the palabok.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Okay, five.
Chicken? How many chicken?
Two.
And then, this one.
- Let's just get one of those.
- One sea bream, please.
- One.
Yes, one.
- Perfect.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Chef, for our inasal and the fish...
- Yeah.
- Fifteen minutes?
- What do I tell them?
- Fish, 15 minutes.
Inasal in five minutes.
Okay.
We'll serve the fish
and the chicken together with the rice.
Yes.
Be good, be good.
- Be good.
- Okay...
This palabok sauce.
Squid.
A bit of this.
To make it look full.
Palabok is good.
Palabok is ready for Table 7 and 8.
Hi, here's your palabok.
It looks so pretty.
I'll take a picture of it.
Okay, fish, fish, fish.
[Salt-Crusted Sea Bream]
The first fish.
Lemongrass.
Garlic.
Red Onion.
[Salt + Lemongrass]
[Mix]
One fish coming in.
This will take 15 minutes.
- Timer?
- Timer.
[Salt-Crusted Sea Bream]
[After 15 minutes]
Nice.
Okay, thermometer, where are you?
Okay.
Wow, that looks really good.
Not going to lie.
[Salt-Crusted Sea Bream]
Hi! So this is your fish.
So this is salted sea bream.
- Wow, that's huge!
- It looks good!
And this is your sauce.
Do we drizzle the sauce or dip into it?
So what's going to happen is...
You get a piece of fish,
and then you dip it here, or maybe like...
She said we have to dip it.
Enjoy!
- Thank you.
That's really cool.
That's huge!
I didn't expect it to be this big.
- Must be good.
- Yeah, it's good.
I needed something light like this.
The meat is decent.
The lower part's really big,
so it's got a lot of meat.
Absolutely.
Should I dip it into the gising-gising?
This is addicting.
It's good even without the sauce.
The seasoning is really balanced throughout.
The sauce is pretty strong.
Hi!
Yes?
Two?
Here, please.
This is cool.
Here's your menu.
- I'll get your water.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
It seems like all the tables will fill up.
- Should we just get all four?
- Four?
Is that too much?
Sinigang, one.
Palabok.
Okay.
Salt-crusted sea bream, one.
Just wait a moment.
- Thank you.
Are you good here?
Another fish order!
Oh, three fish!
I need to make one more.
Just following up on the inasal.
Inasal coming!
Atchara, atchara, atchara!
Inasal, garlic rice!
Thank you, Chef.
You're welcome.
Here is your inasal.
Wow!
[Table 5 Appetizer & Patience]
[Running Low]
I've only been eating the appetizers.
- The chicken skin.
[Where is our...]
So, which table is already served?
Inasal, fish, garlic rice, gising-gising. Okay.
Okay.
Ay!
Wait, they got served first?
And there's two pala...
Five?
Huh?
Oh, five!
Is that new?
- What is this?
- Following up on inasal.
Are there five palabok orders?
Five.
- Five?
- Five.
Okay.
This and... When will the food be served?
Oh, one more...
What's that? Ah, papaya pickle.
Yes, refill this side dish, and...
One more papaya pickle and the other one is?
- Chicken skin?
- One Coke Zero, please.
Okay.
When is the food coming...
Let's ask later.
Coke Zero.
Thank you. When will the food be ready?
I'm sorry?
The food... when will it be ready?
Faster, faster?
Ah, okay. You want us to hurry.
Okay, okay, okay.
- Sorry, sorry.
- It's okay.
It's hard to get the right balance
with such a big order.
Wow, this is
- the most stressful...
- Oil, please.
- palabok order ever.
- Okay.
It looks nice.
Okay.
One.
- Two.
- Thank you, Chef.
Three.
Thank you.
- Okay?
- Four, five. Okay, complete.
Thank you, Chef.
- Thank you, Chef.
- Thank God.
Thank you.
What is this?
- Wow.
- It looks interesting.
- Palabok.
- I regret I didn't order 2 of them.
- So for the...
- Cala?
Calamansi...
Squeeze.
Ah, so that's how it's done with calamansi.
Wow, this is really unique.
So, I guess we eat this with a fork?
The noodles are cooked really well.
It's worth the wait.
It's delicious.
I don't think
I've ever tried noodles like this.
Are these spicy chewy noodles?
- It's kinda like spicy chewy noodles.
- It does feel that way.
What's that called again?
The thing mostly used in dietary products...
Something like umutgasari.
Right, it does remind me of that as well.
The noodles are good.
Wow, to be eating local food
right in the middle of Seoul.
I feel like we'll have to wait again
until the next one.
- Two inasal.
- Did they order garlic rice?
- All done.
- Okay.
Sorry for the delay.
Alright, fish!
Fish next.
This is done, this is done.
Hello!
Chicken inasal.
Enjoy!
Hello. So, this is your chicken inasal.
Place one over there...
Chicken, two.
Let me check. Excuse me.
I guess it's one per order, right?
I think this is the dish
that takes the longest.
One more inasal for Table 5.
This... right here.
Ah! One more inasal!
- Wait.
- Okay.
Ah, what is that?
I'm sorry, the inasal
will be coming out in a bit.
Again, sorry for the delay.
Thank you for your patience.
[The wait continues]
[New Table No.6]
Yes?
One sinigang.
And then...
Palabok.
Inasal.
Okay, please wait a moment.
Every time you come in, I'm scared.
Okay, we got new order. We got sinigang.
One palabok, one inasal.
Sinigang and palabok again.
Yes!
[Inasal Grilling in Progress!]
- That's to speed it up, right?
- Yes.
So it gets coated better.
Oh, I'm getting sleepy.
Here's the appetizer.
[Other Table Getting Served...]
So, this is your palabok.
The sinigang.
Inasal coming, coming.
- I'll put some design into it.
- Yeah.
Art.
Atchara.
There we go!
Yum!
I'm hungry.
You're hungry? You poor thing...
There you go!
One inasal!
- This is good to go?
- Yes!
Table 6?
Yes, Table 6.
Hello, sorry for the wait,
this is your chicken inasal.
Please enjoy.
- Wow, it's really big.
- Exactly.
I think they got the order wrong.
They got served before us.
Yeah, looks like our order went to their table.
Okay, coming in.
Then you make your design.
I'll put lime.
Yeah, there we go, okay.
And then, coriander, onion... We can put chili.
Let's put a tomato.
Hold on, hold on. We got a little magic to do.
Wow.
Okay.
[Salt-Crusted Sea Bream Completed]
- Service. - Service.
Who ordered the fish?
Please double-check, Chef, the table.
They're Table 1, but... Wait, wait, wait, wait!
- I'll ask, I'll ask.
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Hi guys, did you order fish?
- Yeah.
Okay, sorry for the wait.
It takes 20 minutes to cook.
Didn't they also come after us?
They got served with their fish dish.
Maybe we're not getting ours...
Was this it?
I think there was a mix-up with the order.
Excuse me?
Yes?
We finished the dish?
The fish?
Yeah, fish and one chicken.
Okay. I'm so sorry for the wait.
Let me get back.
Are we still getting our food?
Guys!
The fish Chef served to Table 1
should've gone to Table 5.
Where did Chef serve it?
To Table 1.
Why?
Both Table 6 and Table 5 have inasal,
but Table 5 needs it more.
They ordered first, yes...
Earlier, I asked for the inasal at Table 6...
[A moment ago]
There we go!
- Is this good to go?
- Yes!
Table 6?
Yes, Table 6.
Six, seven, six...
Huh? It's already two?
Chef? Oh, he's not here.
Chef served the fish...
Oh, my gosh.
Okay, now, my next agenda is
to buy the thing I wanted to try.
This one?
Fermented bread!
Wow, look at this place!
Wow, there's like a...
They make it at the back!
Hello.
Fermented bread?
And one like this.
Kinda want to try these also.
One also.
And this. I want to get this, too.
I'm getting so many things.
Thank you.
What if I try it now?
- Yeah.
- Let's try it.
Okay.
I'm curious.
So...
Okay, okay, okay...
It looks sticky.
Cheers!
My hand is shaking.
One fell.
Not so sweet.
It's like a crossbreed
between bread and rice cake.
Rice cake.
I like it.
I like the stickiness of it.
You really get to feel
the country in the market.
Yeah.